Dad, I gotta go!
爸  我得去（尿尿）
Come on, you can hold it.
拜托  我能忍住它
I don't think so.
我不这样认为
Sandy, take that out of your mouth.
Sandy  拿那个出你的嘴
- I'm touching... - Gran.
- 我好感动…… - 奶奶
Dad, I still gotta go!
爸  我还是得去
Fine. Just go behind one of those lumpy things and make it fast.
好吧  只要去后面那些成块的东西（中）的一个 并且做得快一点
- Something bit me! - I don't blame it.
- 有东西咬我   - 我不责怪它
-Dad, can I take a turn carrying him? -No.
爸  能不能轮到我扛他 -不
- How about now? - No.
- 现在怎么样 - 不
- Now? - No.
- 现在呢   - 不
-Now? -I can do this all day long.
-现在呢  -我可以做这个一整天那么长（的时间）
No, no, no and still no.
不  不  不还是不
I'm not dying on an empty stomach.
我不能死在空腹上
Grug, we're all pretty tired!
Grug  我们都很累了
We'll eat when we get there.
我们会吃当我们到达那里
It's taking too long!
它花费太久